[SPEAKER_00] இது கஷ்டத்த தாண்டி வர்ற ஒரு
[SPEAKER_00] ஒரு நாள் ஒரு விவசாயியோட கழுதை,
[SPEAKER_00] சரி... அந்த மிருகம் ரொம்ப நேரமா பாவம்
[SPEAKER_00] விவசாயி என்ன பண்றதுன்னு
[SPEAKER_00] Finally, he decided the animal was old.
[SPEAKER_00] and the whale needed to be covered up anyway. It just...
[SPEAKER_00] guess wasn't worth it to retrieve the donkey.
[SPEAKER_00] all of his neighbors to come over and help him.
[SPEAKER_00] all grab the shovel and began to shovel dirt.
[SPEAKER_00] into the well. At first, the donkey realises.
[SPEAKER_00] what was happening and cried horribly. Then...
[SPEAKER_00] to everyone's amazement he quieted down.
[SPEAKER_00] few shovel loads later, the farmer finally looked at the
[SPEAKER_00] down the well. He was astonished at what he saw with...
[SPEAKER_00] each shovel of dirt that hit his back, the donkey.
[SPEAKER_00] was doing something amazing. He would shake it off and take it.
[SPEAKER_00] a step up as the farmers neighbors continued to
[SPEAKER_00] shovel dirt on top of the enemy, he would shake it off.
[SPEAKER_00] and take a step up. Pretty soon everyone was in
[SPEAKER_00] as the doggy stepped up over the edge of the...
[SPEAKER_00] well and happily trotted off. Life is...
[SPEAKER_00] going to shovel dirt on you all kinds of dirt.
[SPEAKER_00] The trick to getting out of the well is to shake it.
[SPEAKER_00] off and take a step up each of our troubles.
[SPEAKER_00] is a stepping stone. We can get out of the deepest
[SPEAKER_00] just by not stopping never giving up.
[SPEAKER_00] Shake it off and take a step up.
[SPEAKER_00] you're not following the Biz Thoughts project, you're probably
[SPEAKER_00] never going to see us again but if you are can bring
[SPEAKER_00] threats. You're on a journey of continuous growth.